https://journeycare.org/terms-use/

Careers
Why JourneyCare?
Share your story
1-844-6-JOURNEY(844-656-8763)
Call us 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.
TapCloud App for Patients and Caregivers
Is there a cost to hospice and palliative care?
Volunteer Training/Events
Why Volunteer?
Navigation
About Us»- Expert Care Along the Journey- Our Mission, Vision and Values- Service Area Map and Locations- Testimonials- Our History- Our Key Partners- Our Leadership- Boards of Directors & Trustees- JourneyCare FoundationServices»- Hospice Care- JourneyCare’s Hospice CareCenters- Palliative Medicine- Pediatric Care- Grief Support- TapCloud- Request Medical RecordsCareers»- Why JourneyCare?- Benefits- Our Mission, Vision and Values- Career Opportunities- Contact Human ResourcesNews & Events»- Events- Media Center- Publications- Care and Support BlogBlogContact Us- Help Spread the Word- Sign up for eNews- Share your storyLiving With»- Understanding Your Illness- Navigating Care Options for Those with Serious Illness- Questions to Ask Your Doctor- Living with Hospice Care- See Our CareCenters- Care at Home- Integrative Care Services- Music-Thanatology- Specialized Care for Memory Loss- Alleviating Pain & Symptoms with Palliative Medicine- Hospice & Palliative Medicine: The Difference- TapCloud App for Patients and Caregivers- Is there a cost to hospice and palliative care?- Advance Care Planning- Helpful Resources- Community ProgramsFamily»- How Life Changes When a Family Member Gets Sick- Caregiver Education & Support- Grief Support- One-on-One Support- Group Support- Support for Children and Teens- Grief Resources- Honoring & Remembering- Memorial Services- Memorial Bricks- Grateful Family & Friends- Helpful Caregiver Resources- Jewish Care Services- We Honor Veterans- Pet Peace of Mind- Community ProgramsSpecialized Care»- When Your Child is Diagnosed with a Serious Illness- Expert Care for Your Child- Child Life Specialist- Making Family Moments Count- Helpful Family ResourcesHow Can I Help?»- Overview- Apply to Become a JourneyCare Volunteer- Volunteer Opportunities- Volunteer Training/Events- Why Volunteer?- Youth Volunteer Opportunities- Corporate Volunteer Opportunities- Volunteer PortalJourneyCare»- Overview- Donate to JourneyCare- Ways You Can Donate- Comfort and Joy- Memorial Giving- Leaving a Legacy- Sign Up to Receive Foundation News- Become a Corporate Partner- Become a Corporate Volunteer- Board of TrusteesFor Clinical»- Make a Referral- The Right Time- The JourneyCare Difference- Our Key Partners- Physician Billing Guide- Education for Staff- Partnering To Educate Leaders of Tomorrow
JourneyCare hereby expressly disclaims any liability or responsibility for the content, use, dissemination or otherwise of any information contained herein, or any information which any visitor to this website may be directed to via any links or otherwise.
The information on the JourneyCare website is for general informational purposes only, and is not intended to provide medical or other professional advice. If you are concerned you may have a health problem, you should contact your doctor for specific advice about your situation or course of treatment.
You should not rely on information provided on JourneyCare.org as a substitute for personal medical attention, diagnosis or treatment by a qualified medical professional. You should never disregard medical advice or delay in seeking care because of something you have read on this website. Never discontinue treatment or medication without first consulting your physician.
While JourneyCare makes reasonable efforts to provide accurate and complete information, we cannot guarantee the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of the information or materials contained on this website. Visitors to this website assume the risk of using any information or materials contained herein.
JourneyCare provides links to other websites for your convenience; however, we assume no responsibility for the content or information contained on any other site. Nor do we recommend, endorse or approve any materials, products or services which may be available or advertised on any other site.
Please be advised that JourneyCare cannot guarantee the confidentiality and security of electronic mail submitted via the Internet. JourneyCare reserves the rights to the information on this website, including the right of distribution. Information on this website may be protected under copyright laws.
WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY
We understand, acknowledge and respect any individual’s right to privacy and the concerns one may have in regard to privacy and security. We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of information provided by our patients, as well as, general users of our website.
IMPORTANT NOTE! The JourneyCare Privacy Policy is a separate document that governs how medical information about you may be used and disclosed by JourneyCare.
MEDICAL DISCLAIMER. IF THIS IS A MEDICAL EMERGENCY, PLEASE IMMEDIATELY CALL EMERGENCY PERSONNEL (911) TO GET PROMPT MEDICAL ATTENTION. DO NOT RELY ON ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS FOR ASSISTANCE IN REGARD TO YOUR IMMEDIATE, URGENT MEDICAL NEEDS. THIS E-MAIL IS NOT DESIGNED TO FACILITATE MEDICAL EMERGENCIES. JOURNEYCARE CANNOT GUARANTEE RESPONSE TIMES IF YOU CHOOSE TO USE THIS E-MAIL IN THE EVENT OF A MEDICAL EMERGENCY.
PERSONAL INFORMATION.
A visitor can access and browse our entire site at any time without providing any personal information. We do not collect information that would personally identify you unless you choose to provide it.
In addition, JourneyCare does not share any personally identifiable information of any individual with any third party unrelated to JourneyCare, except in situations where we must provide information for legal purposes or investigations, or if so directed by the patient through a proper authorization.
Forms
Our website contains forms through which users may request information or supply feedback to us. In some cases, telephone numbers, email addresses or return addresses are required so that we can supply requested information to you, and in other cases, correct names and addresses are required to process credit card payments.
After you fill out a form, we may contact you with follow-up information (unless you have checked an “opt-out” box on the form). We do not provide any information supplied on our web forms to any outside organization for any reason (other than where we may be required to by law, or as necessary to process credit card information). We do not save this personal information for any other reason.
Surveys
Occasionally, we may survey visitors to our site. The information from these surveys is used in aggregate form to help us understand the needs of our visitors so that we can improve our site. We generally do not ask for information in surveys that would personally identify you. If we do request contact information for follow-up, you may decline to provide it. If survey respondents provide personal information (such as an email address) in a survey, it is shared only with those people who need to see it to respond to the question or request.
Email
“Phishing” is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an email that looks like it is from JourneyCare asking you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through email.
User Name and Password
In the event you access any Service requiring a User Name and Password, you are solely responsible for keeping such User Name and Password strictly confidential.
NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION
JourneyCare collects non-personal information such as website usage, traffic patterns, site performance and related statistics based on our tracking of your visits to the website.
IP Addresses
The web server automatically collects the IP (which stands for Internet Protocol) address of the computers that access our site. An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you access the Internet. It is not truly personally identifiable information because many different individuals can access the Internet via the same computer. We use this information in aggregate form to understand how our site is being used and how we can better serve visitors.
Please note that although such information is not personally identifiable, we can determine from an IP address a visitor’s Internet Service Provider and the geographic location of his or her point of connectivity.
First Party Cookies
We collect information about visitors to our site using “first party cookies”, which are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser. Cookies are never associated with specific personal identities. First party cookies are distinct from third party cookies that they are created and directly served by the company hosting the website.
We use two types of “cookies” on this site:
We use persistent cookies to recognize a repeat visitor, enabling us the opportunity to offer the visitor information from a previous visit.
We use session cookies to track a visitor’s path through our site during a visit, to help us understand how people use our site.
You can delete our cookies at any time. The “help” section, located on the toolbar of most browsers, will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie or how to disable cookies altogether. Since cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of our website’s best features, we recommend that you leave them turned on.
SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION
Please note that our forms are encrypted to protect your privacy. Once the information is sent to our site, it is kept in secure databases where it is not available to users on the Internet. While we sometimes ask for credit card numbers or certain service transactions, and either pass them on to a credit card processing service or process them manually, we do not store credit card numbers online.
JourneyCare periodically reviews and modifies, where appropriate, its security policies and procedures. We use reasonable care to protect your personally identifiable and confidential information provided by you to our site. JourneyCare has in place a security program that seeks to mitigate this risk substantially.
DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY
MATERIALS, SERVICES AND OTHER INFORMATION ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” BY JOURNEYCARE FOR EDUCATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY. JOURNEYCARE MAKES NO EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR USE, TITLE OR NON INFRINGEMENT.
PLEASE NOTE THAT, BY ITS VERY NATURE, A WEBSITE CANNOT BE ABSOLUTELY PROTECTED AGAINST INTENTIONAL OR MALICIOUS INTRUSION ATTEMPTS. FURTHERMORE, JOURNEYCARE DOES NOT CONTROL THE DEVICES OR COMPUTERS OR THE INTERNET OVER WHICH YOU MAY CHOOSE TO SEND CONFIDENTIAL PERSONAL INFORMATION AND CANNOT, THEREFORE, PREVENT SUCH INTERCEPTIONS OF COMPROMISES TO YOUR INFORMATION WHILE IN TRANSIT TO JOURNEYCARE.
THEREFORE, JOURNEYCARE HEREBY MAKES NO GUARANTEE AS TO SECURITY, INTEGRITY OR CONFIDENTIALITY OF ANY INFORMATION TRANSMITTED TO OR FROM THIS WEBSITE, OR STORED WITHIN THIS WEBSITE.
BEYOND OUR REASONABLE CARE TO SAFEGUARD YOUR INFORMATION WHILE IN TRANSIT, JOURNEYCARE CANNOT AND DOES NOT GUARANTEE THE ABSOLUTE SECURITY OF ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS OR TRANSMISSIONS SINCE ANY TRANSMISSION MADE OVER THE INTERNET BY ANY ORGANIZATION OR ANY INDIVIDUAL RUNS THE RISK OF INTERCEPTION.
IN ADDITION, WE HEREBY MAKE NO GUARANTEE AS TO SECURITY, INTEGRITY OR CONFIDENTIALITY OF ANY INFORMATION TRANSMITTED TO OR FROM THIS WEBSITE, OR STORED WITHIN THIS WEBSITE.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
YOU ASSUME THE SOLE RISK OF TRANSMITTING YOUR INFORMATION AS IT RELATES TO THE USE OF THIS WEBSITE, AND FOR ANY DATA CORRUPTIONS, INTENTIONAL INTERCEPTIONS, INTRUSIONS OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO INFORMATION, OR OF ANY DELAYS, INTERRUPTIONS TO OR FAILURES PREVENTING THE USE THIS WEBSITE.
IN NO EVENT SHALL JOURNEYCARE BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR MONETARY DAMAGES, INCLUDING FEES, AND PENALTIES IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF MATERIALS POSTED ON THIS SITE OR CONNECTIVITY TO OR FROM THIS SITE TO ANY OTHER SITE.
JOURNEYCARE MAY CHANGE THIS PRIVACY POLICY WITHOUT NOTICE TO YOU.
Other services provided by JourneyCare on this Website may require you to agree to additional terms.
BY USING THIS WEBSITE, YOU ACCEPT THESE TERMS.
If you have any questions about our privacy policy or our use of information gathered through our Web site, please contact us.
Last updated: 3/14/2018
Make a Donation
Career Opportunities
UPCOMING EVENTSview full calendar>
Featured Video
1-844-6-JOURNEY
Contact
Privacy
Non-Discrimination
Terms of Use
Navigation
About Us»- Expert Care Along the Journey- Our Mission, Vision and Values- Service Area Map and Locations- Testimonials- Our History- Our Key Partners- Our Leadership- Boards of Directors & Trustees- JourneyCare FoundationServices»- Hospice Care- JourneyCare’s Hospice CareCenters- Palliative Medicine- Pediatric Care- Grief Support- TapCloud- Request Medical RecordsCareers»- Why JourneyCare?- Benefits- Our Mission, Vision and Values- Career Opportunities- Contact Human ResourcesNews & Events»- Events- Media Center- Publications- Care and Support BlogBlogContact Us- Help Spread the Word- Sign up for eNews- Share your storyLiving With»- Understanding Your Illness- Navigating Care Options for Those with Serious Illness- Questions to Ask Your Doctor- Living with Hospice Care- See Our CareCenters- Care at Home- Integrative Care Services- Music-Thanatology- Specialized Care for Memory Loss- Alleviating Pain & Symptoms with Palliative Medicine- Hospice & Palliative Medicine: The Difference- TapCloud App for Patients and Caregivers- Is there a cost to hospice and palliative care?- Advance Care Planning- Helpful Resources- Community ProgramsFamily»- How Life Changes When a Family Member Gets Sick- Caregiver Education & Support- Grief Support- One-on-One Support- Group Support- Support for Children and Teens- Grief Resources- Honoring & Remembering- Memorial Services- Memorial Bricks- Grateful Family & Friends- Helpful Caregiver Resources- Jewish Care Services- We Honor Veterans- Pet Peace of Mind- Community ProgramsSpecialized Care»- When Your Child is Diagnosed with a Serious Illness- Expert Care for Your Child- Child Life Specialist- Making Family Moments Count- Helpful Family ResourcesHow Can I Help?»- Overview- Apply to Become a JourneyCare Volunteer- Volunteer Opportunities- Volunteer Training/Events- Why Volunteer?- Youth Volunteer Opportunities- Corporate Volunteer Opportunities- Volunteer PortalJourneyCare»- Overview- Donate to JourneyCare- Ways You Can Donate- Comfort and Joy- Memorial Giving- Leaving a Legacy- Sign Up to Receive Foundation News- Become a Corporate Partner- Become a Corporate Volunteer- Board of TrusteesFor Clinical»- Make a Referral- The Right Time- The JourneyCare Difference- Our Key Partners- Physician Billing Guide- Education for Staff- Partnering To Educate Leaders of Tomorrow
+
100%
-
JourneyCare | Copyright © 2020 | All Rights Reserved
